### Juan González Cabezuelo



### Personal details

•

Juan González Cabezuelo



juangccd@gmail.com



63716370



Rafael Cansino Vega 7 41940 Tomares



github.com/juangccd



linkedin.com/in/ juan-gonzález-cabezuelo

## Skills

HTML and CSS3

BOOTSTRAP

SASS

JAVA

JAVASCRIPT

PHP

WORDPRESS

SHOPIFY

MYSQL

# Languages

English ••••

### **Profile**

Support Technician with experience in the workplace and dealing with the user. With excellent customer skills and a solid knowledge of programming in client and server environments with Java, SpringBoot, PHP, Angular and MySQL. Able to learn easily and with a desire to improve.

### Education

# Higher Degree in Web Application Development

Sep 2019 - Jun 2021

IES Alixar, Castilleja de la Cuesta, Sevilla

## **Employment**

### **Technical support**

Mar 2021 - Jul 2021

Ceroone Technology SL, Gines, Sevilla

- Monitoring the operation of the systems and input commands.
- Extensive experience in Wordpress and Shopify as well as in modifying Plugins and code in them.

#### **Energy Advisor**

Dec 2019 - Jun 2021

Transcom Worlwide, Sevilla

- Study of the commercial and marketing activity of the competition proposing alternative commercial actions.
- Maintenance, loyalty and development of client portfolio.

## **Open Webinars Courses**

**Docker DevOps Profesional** 

Bootstrap 4: Responsive Design and Layout

**Bootstrap 4: Components** 

HTML5 and CSS3 course

Sass course

**PHP Course: Expanding Concepts** 

**WordPress Theme Creation Course** 

Course website administration with WordPress in a professional way

**Development environment for WordPress with Docker** 

**Gutenberg in WordPress 5** 

**Git Course**